Senpai?
Why?
Why did you come here?
Now everything I did was in vain!
Why do you think I—
Shut up!
"Live on"?
"Become a normal person"?
Who the hell wished for that?
Who the hell asked for that crap?!
How unpleasant!
How utterly unpleasant!
I'm the one who should be feeling unpleasant!
Anyway, I refuse to stand for this!
I don't want a life that was
built on your sacrifice.
A future like that...
holds no meaning at all!
Why don't you understand that?!
Why was that so difficult for you to understand?
I never thought I'd run into you here,
Kanbara Yayoi.
Long time no see.
Hop you've grown, Izumin.
I want to kick her.
What are you after?
What exactly is your relationship with Kanbara Akihito?
"What"? Akkun's my little fella!
Oh, and I didn't mean anything bunny by that—
I couldn't take it any more.
Don't worry.
If you hadn't done it, I would have.
Answer my questions.
What is your relationship
with the immortal half-shade?
What are you after?
I carrot believe you'd ask such stupid questions. You're no fun anymore, Izumin.
You shouldn't have grown up
to be that kind of adult—
It's not like I chose to be like this.
Izumi...
Izumi-neesan!
A double!
When will you stop dragging these kids into us adults' nonsense?
The Spirit Hunters' Association has already made its move, you know?
Hiro'omi-kun, Mitsuki-chan.
Akihito and Mirai-chan are more than
just a dreamshade and a spirit hunter—
they're special.
I leave them in your care!
To be continued!
Wait!
Nee-san!
Right now,
shouldn't that beam of light take priority?
Geez!
「Gray World」
「Final Episode」
How can anyone call that
absurd thing a dreamshade?
Don't ask me!
You were the one who was harboring it to begin with!
That's just the core.
In truth, everything around us was inside you.
No wonder my back's been killing me.
This is no time to be joking around!
Senpai,
have you come up with anything yet?
What do you mean?
Like a weakness or something!
You know, maybe it has
sensitive armpits like you.
Armpits?
Where exactly?!
Then... do you have something you hate?
Anything will do.
Something I hate, huh?
Capelin with roe?
Capelin with roe!
Think it's mad now?
Don't ask me!
Kuriyama-san!
Did you just do that?
I think so.
Wait, you have a shade hand now?
That shadestone was a part of the
shade beyond the horizon—a part of you?
Yeah.
Senpai, you hold a part of its
powers in your hand right now!
I'm not sure how we'll manage,
but if you can stand up to it...
...then it might be worth getting closer.
Looks like it hasn't finished eating just yet.
Is that how strong the shade from beyond the horizon is?
Or does that reflect how
strong-willed Kuriyama Mirai is?
The latter, obviously.
Wow, you're pretty handsome.
Not my type, though.
It seems some of my powers have returned thanks to the efforts of those two.
Well, should be enough to defeat you—
I'm not interested in you.
Sure took your time today, eh?
You kept me waiting.
It's grown rather powerful, don't you think?
By feeding off the Hollow Shade you had at your place,
it's finally starting to take its rightful shape.
Unfortunately for you,
I stalk anyone who so much as lays a finger on
my little sister, waiting for the chance to crush them.
Three-on-one, huh?
No.
Four-on-one.
Mitsuki?
Just because I was the last-born,
I've had to sit tight at home all my life.
It's about time I moved on from that.
Likewise.
I was the one who originally wielded that scythe.
I have to take responsibility for my actions.
Goodness me,
you people are getting along pretty well all of a sudden.
Nee-sama!
Crap!
Nobody can get in our way now.
How much farther?
We're almost there!
All right. The keys are in the ignition.
Wha—
Do you have a license, Senpai?
It's not like this is a public road!
Hurry up and hop on, Kuriyama-san!
Hey—
Gosh!
On the handlebar?!
There are dreamshades up ahead.
From below, too!
Way to go, Kuriyama-san!
So do I just keep going straight?
I don't know.
But you better go as fast as you can!
After all,
it's too late to hit the brakes!
Senpai!
No way!
That was absurd.
This whole place is absurd.
In other words,
you're absurd.
Me?!
Somehow we made it, though.
Where are we?
Huh?
Our opponent's in a panic too.
You can tell?
I can't.
But that's how I feel.
I'm sure things will work out!
That's kind of unlike you.
I don't know what you're talking about.
That said,
I, Kuriyama Mirai,
am feeling optimistic to an unpleasant degree!
What are you running your mouth off for?!
Wait, can it really hear us?
How should I know?
Go for it, Kuriyama-san!
Kuriyama-san...
Akkey...
It's almost time.
Now that the shade beyond the horizon is free of Kuriyama Mirai,
it will draw every other dreamshade
out there into an ever-widening spiral
and destroy the world.
What now,
Izumi-san?
Kuriyama-san?
Kuriyama-san.
Kuriyama-san!
Don't kill us.
Disgusting.
You monster.
I'm so scared.
Are these my memories?
Senpai?
Your younger siblings don't know when to give up,
just like you.
Go for it, big bro.
Mitsuki?
Leaving this to Izumi-neesama means
admitting that we're as powerless as ever.
Nothing will change.
Got it.
Leave it to your dear Onii-chan!
Hiro'omi-senpai's so creepy.
I know, right?
Why are you in such a rush?
That's the look.
That's the look I wanted to see on you.
That scared and panicked look you try to hide
as you struggle to take me down!
Shut up!
Are you that afraid?
Oh no, I don't suppose you fancy me?
Or do you just not want your siblings to find out about your past?
Shut up! A spirit hunter who gave in to shades has no right to speak!
Listen to yourself.
Aren't we birds of a feather?
We both harbor shades in our bodies.
Did you know that,
little brother?
Izumi-neesan...
Shut up!
Shut up! Shut up! Shut up!
Sure, we may be the same in that regard,
but I have yet to abandon
my pride as a human being.
Don't lump me together
with the likes of you.
Oh please, spare me the dramatics.
Nee-san...
Wh-What's going on?
It's probably something similar to what showed up back in the Hollow Shadow.
Hiro'omi-senpai!
Yui?!
Close your eyes, Kuriyama-san.
Just do it.
Okay!
Don't be swayed.
They say that dreamshades are formed from the twisted human heart and the hatred within, right?
Well, this is a manifestation of the weakness in our hearts.
Didn't I tell you back when we first met?
I told you that the same goes for me.
I'm here by your side.
We met each other.
The world changed.
Don't be a slave to your regrets.
You're not alone anymore.
I'm here for you.
Senpai!
Open your eyes.
What the hell is this?
Let's take them out.
All of them?
Do you have a better idea?
How unpleasant.
Ayaka-san!
Ai-chan!
You guys are okay!
Did we get them all?
Who knows?
Pretty, isn't it?
Y-Yeah.
What are you so terrified of?
It's okay.
Every last bit of you is me.
All of it used to be inside me.
Including that sickening envy,
the despair over the fact that I'll never be human,
the sorrow of being abandoned,
and the regret over hurting someone!
Senpai...
And the selfishness, doubt, hatred, resignation, pettiness, and self-preserving attitude!
I won't let any of it outside!
It all belongs to me!
I'll be the one to carry it all!
I'm the immortal half-shade, you know?
Senpai...
Senpai,
could you come over here?
I'm sorry.
Er, um, uh...
I have...
a request...
A request?
Um, please hold out your hand.
My hand?
Yes.
Please pat my head.
I want you to pat my head.
Kuriyama-san...
Say "thank you."
Thank you.
Say it like you mean it.
So happy...
I'm so happy!
Kuriyama-san!
Kuriyama-san, your legs...
The shade beyond the horizon
has gone back to you,
so this place will crumble away soon,
and I'll probably disappear along with it.
Now that it's gone back to you,
I won't be able to exist.
The real me is long gone, after all.
I'm truly glad to have met you!
Stop it!
I'm truly glad to have fallen in love with you—
Stop! Don't say it!
Thank you so very much!
Kuriyama-san!
Hang on! This can't be happening!
Nobody knows if this was all predestined from the start,
or if it only happened thanks to Kuriyama-san's efforts.
But I definitely want to believe it was the latter.
Anyway, the shade from beyond the horizon came back to me,
and peace was restored to the world.
100 yen? Are you for real?!
I'm off!
Oh, morning!
Good morning.
Be careful out there.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
She dozed off!
Come on, Sakura-chan! Wake up!
Dreamshades exist as they always have,
and spirit hunters make a living off them as they always have.
Ayaka-san and Ai-chan went back to their place, too.
80% Milk
Banana
Au Lait
Fujima Miroku went missing,
and the Spirit Hunters' Association wrapped everything up nicely
by disavowing all knowledge of his actions.
One thing did change: Hiro'omi replaced
Izumi-san as the head of the Nase family.
But that didn't affect our lives much.
Nee-san...
One day, you will also come to understand.
Forgive me.
Izumi-neesan.
You've always been my role model.
I've lived my entire life wanting to be like you.
But I'm done with that.
I won't turn out like you did.
I understand now.
When you try to live up to your ideals, sometimes it might not work out.
But nothing good can come out of giving up on them.
You won't be able to protect yourself or those important to you.
You've grown stronger, Hiro'omi.
Now listen here, Hiro'omi.
You're the Nase family's—
I know!
Say no more. Not now.
Literature Club
As usual, Mitsuki remains cooped up in the
clubroom and showers me with verbal abuse.
If you know that good will prevail over evil in the end,
isn't it a waste of time to continue reading?
That's what entertainment's all about, don't you think?
Cut it out!
Hey, it's only natural to keep one's hands warm in winter.
There's nothing strange about what I'm doing.
It's totally creepy-crawly!
Three out of ten.
However, Kuriyama Mirai's no longer here.
In the end, I lost.
TARGET: 50,000 YEN
A future built on Kuriyama Mirai's sacrifice holds no meaning at all.
That's what I yelled out back then, but here I am, having accepted—and living in—that very future.
I'm sure this is what Kuriyama-san's saying right about now:
"Serves you right."
How unpleasant.
Literature Club Plans for December
Just as there is light even at night,
rature Club Plans for December
ub Plans for December
b Plans for December
Plans for December
Club Plans for December
ure Club Plans for December
ature Club Plans for December
rature Club Plans for December
just as there are shadows during the day,
the world will never be free of darkness.
At the same time, it will also never be overcome by it.
Dyed in that half-baked hue, the universe will continue to move on and set events in motion.
And in the midst of all that, I...
Tearing the silence to shreds
Seijaku wo kirisaku you
The time has come
Otozureta no wa
For us to cross paths
Hitsuzen to shite no kaikou
It's a meeting we were fated to have
Bokura no tame ni
My eyes filled with regret, I see you
Koukai wo nageku me ni utsuru kimi wa sou
U-Um...
Clad in anguish
Urei wo matotte
Bespectacled...
Blossoming beautifully
Utsukushiku saita
Basically, I love the bespectacled Kuriyama-san!
I can see the flower bringing joy to people's lives
Dareka no seimei ni tokeru hana
Can you see it too?
Nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
I'm sure you can
Kitto
How unpleasant.
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
Kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
Nobody knows if this was all predestined from the start,
or if it only happened thanks to Kuriyama-san's efforts.
We'll start over and over again until we succeed
Nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteku Start Line
Maybe my feelings for Kuriyama-san reached her.
For the sake of a fresh future
Kako to wa chigau asu wo
And that's how I reunited with Kuriyama Mirai.
If our story had ended after a reunion like that,
We'll start realizing our very own hopes and dreams
Futari dake no kibou egaku Start Line
I don't think any story in this world would be worth telling.
I have never said goodbye
I never say goodbye
Oh right, Kuriyama-san.
And I never will
Itsudatte sou sa
You forgot something.
Could you do me a favor and put these glasses on?