「Gray World」
「Final Episode」
80% Milk
Banana
Au Lait
Literature Club
TARGET: 50,000 YEN
Literature Club Plans for December
rature Club Plans for December
ub Plans for December
b Plans for December
Plans for December
Club Plans for December
ure Club Plans for December
ature Club Plans for December
rature Club Plans for December
Tearing the silence to shreds
Seijaku wo kirisaku you
The time has come
Otozureta no wa
For us to cross paths
Hitsuzen to shite no kaikou
It's a meeting we were fated to have
Bokura no tame ni
My eyes filled with regret, I see you
Koukai wo nageku me ni utsuru kimi wa sou
Clad in anguish
Urei wo matotte
Blossoming beautifully
Utsukushiku saita
I can see the flower bringing joy to people's lives
Dareka no seimei ni tokeru hana
Can you see it too?
Nee kimi ni mo mieru darou
I'm sure you can
Kitto
Let's paint over all the mistakes we've made
Kasaneta ayamachi nurikaeyou
We'll start over and over again until we succeed
Nando demo ii sa kurikaeshiteku Start Line
For the sake of a fresh future
Kako to wa chigau asu wo
We'll start realizing our very own hopes and dreams
Futari dake no kibou egaku Start Line
I have never said goodbye
I never say goodbye
And I never will
Itsudatte sou sa